Dreadened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
The Knights of the Golden Dawn fought to quell the Diamond Kingdom's invasion of Khitan.
Meanwhile, Yami confronted his fellow Captain Vongens with a long-held suspicion.
Vongens, if you don't mind, lose the mask.
I understand, Yami. You are suspicious of me, aren't you?
You think I might be the leader of the Eye of the Midnight Sun?
Very well.
Asta and Yuno, meeting again at last, expressed a renewed conviction to achieve their shared goal.
We're aiming to become the Wizard King.
At the same time, however, a new force was stirring in the Diamond Kingdom.
Thank you.
What's the deal with you, kid? Are you physically incapable of not fighting something? For some kind of disorder?
My body just moved on its own! Really?
Come on. You were beat up already and you fought anyway.
You're getting checked out. That head needs looking at.
Well, yeah, now it does, thanks to you!
Hey, come on in, Yami. Brought someone to see me?
Who's that guy?
He's a lot less impressive looking than this fancy tower. But don't let that fool you. This guy's actually the kingdom's best quack.
You're so mean.
He's a real powerful recovery mage who's done a pretty decent job keeping my arms attached to my body. So I figured he could take a look at yours.
That isn't helping, sir!
Nice to meet you. The name's Owen, and I report directly to the Wizard King himself. How can I help?
Yes, sir! I'm Asta! Nice to meet you, too!
Of course. I've heard all about you. Yami gets chatty when he's drinking.
What did he say?
Well, he's told a few stories about how your sword can nullify magic. Who knew something like that was even possible?
This guy reports directly to the Wizard King? It doesn't take a genius to figure out he must be seriously awesome!
Well, I gotta see a man about a dog, so... I'm gonna win today. I can feel it in my bones.
Got some gambling to do? Good luck, sir!
You know, that captain of yours is an awfully imposing man for being so much younger than me.
It's kind of irritating. Still, for all his growling, he's not a bad guy.
Yeah.
Okay, go on and have a seat.
Yes, sir!
Now, let's see here.
Water recovery magic. Koala operation.
Wow, look at that. They got you pretty good, but don't worry.
My spell sees through the body of a person it envelops, so I can zero in on the affected areas and heal them with extreme precision.
Yami's no slouch, but you've got some pretty amazing muscles there yourself.
Thanks, I train hard.
And now for some mana to help with the healing.
I thought I was never going to get out of there.
Now that the Golden Dawn's five jillion prisoners have been transported, I can track down Asta and go.
Whoa! What the heck is that?
Some kind of jellyfish healing spell?
Asta.
Hmm?
Oh, sorry, Finral. Have you been waiting long?
It's fine, Asta. Don't worry about me. It's not like we could go before Yami's back anyway.
Yo!
Wow.
You cleaned up.
Yep, I knew it was my lucky day today.
Um, what do you have in the sack?
Less talking and more portaling.
Yes, sir.
Okay, listen up.
Some of you might have noticed, we've racked up so many stars lately that we've actually made it out of the hole.
Which is all thanks to you knuckleheads and the hard work you've been doing.
And so...
That's right, it's meat time!
Wow!
Yeah!
This meat! This meat! That meat! All of me!
Daisy!
Wow!
So yummy!
This is a freaking holiday!
If Yami's treating us, I'm going to eat a whole lifetime's worth of meat!
Marie, I would never allow you to eat such inferior food.
You want to cook a cut of meat like this to between 130 and 140 degrees.
We need a high enough temperature to make sure any nasty bacteria are killed,
so it'll be safe to eat, but not so high that the meat gets tough.
Say, ah!
So good!
Hey, Magna!
Wanna fight to death for this hunk of meat?
No, I don't!
Aw, you're no fun!
Got something to wash it down with, too!
I love today!
Hot! Hot! It's so hot!
Oh, jeez!
Oh, my gosh! Oh, my gosh! Please watch me! It's embarrassing!
So, I guess, it must be hard to eat with those arms.
If you need somebody to feed you, I suppose I would be willing to help. Just this once.
Hey, look! I can eat with my feet now! Pretty cool, huh?
Oh, they're coming up!
All right, Finral, show us the trick.
Oh, um, sure. Right.
Watch! The self-punch!
All right, you're next, Charmy.
My trick instantly disappears in me!
Um, um...
All you did was eat it. That's cheating.
Let's see it, Gray. You're up!
Oh, no! Don't make me! Please!
Shut up and do it!
Ah!
Here goes...
Come on! This is your usual guy!
Here's my trick! The Crackling Magnet Typhoon!
Light on!
Read, shoot, take off!
Oh, I can do some weight training!
That's not a special trick!
Well, guys, I'm actually feeling pretty beat.
I think I'm just gonna call it a day.
Okay, get some shut-eye, Rasta.
Great job, everybody!
Night!
Does Rasta seem a little bit off to you at all?
You're right.
I don't know if I've ever seen him go to bed early before.
He always seems so happy,
but it felt like he was faking it today.
I could see if a drink would cheer him up.
Maybe all he needs is a good death match.
Obviously, the problem is he didn't eat enough meat!
I wonder if something happened.
Ah! Forget I said anything!
Mary!
So, um, listen.
Hmm?
I overheard something while Asta was being healed.
His arms... they're...
They're never going to get better.
What?
No way.
That can't be right.
What?
No way.
That can't be right.
Asta, I believe you were hit with ancient hex magic.
On top of that, your bones have basically disintegrated.
I'm afraid not even my magic will be able to heal you.
A curse.
You have my gratitude for summoning me, human.
If the best recovery mage in the kingdom says that's what happened, it's most likely true.
It can't be...
I thought that I'd found...
Somebody I could fight with.
No, I can't believe it.
He has no magic, and now...
Now he can't even use his only weapon anymore.
Oh no!
So...
Sad!
Asta...
I'm sorry to tell you this, but you'll never wield a sword again.
You'll never wield a sword again.
What now?
Like I'm gonna give up!
Huh?
You got me again, Fate, you big jerk!
But all you did was get me even more fired up!
I'm gonna find a cure for my arms somehow, do you hear me?!
And if that's not possible, then I'll just figure out a way to fight without them!
Without them!
These chains can measure the magic power of anyone they come in contact with, and you have none!
No matter how hard I push myself, I'll never be able to use magic.
You might as well give it all up right now!
You were born a loser, you worthless runt!
So...
I might as well give...
I almost gave up that time, but it's never happening again!
Just you wait and see!
He's fine.
Yeah, kid, you tell him.
Doesn't get much manlier than that!
Yup, that's our Asta!
Sure is.
I'll share my dessert with him later!
After all that's happened, he's still so hopeful!
He is pretty tough.
I won't let him near Marie, but I will give him that much.
That's right, kiddo.
Don't you give up.
I just might know a place where we can find magic that'll help you.
Morning, everybody!
Huh?
There's always someone around making noise or causing trouble. The hideout feels totally deserted.
Did the others already head out somewhere?
It's me.
Maybe they're still sleeping?
Things did get pretty crazy yesterday.
I can feel that key!
If you wanna hide from me, you'll have to do better than that!
It's Noelle and Finral.
What are they up to?
Okay, I think that's just about everybody now.
Did you hear them all trying to be sneaky?
I forgot I had an important errand to run!
Oh, I promised my cousin I would visit her today.
Like, it isn't totally obvious they're running off to find a cure for Asta.
Huh?
I guess since they aren't going on missions, they don't want Yami to find out and get mad.
Plus, you know if Asta found out, he'd tell everybody to focus on their magic night duties and not worry about him.
Looks like a place where you could find some real trouble.
You getting scared on me, Magna?
Yeah, right! If anything, I'm even more excited than I was before!
Magna and Luck are dungeon hunting in the wastelands of the Forsaken Realm.
Hang in there, Asta!
Gosh and Gordon are researching hexes in the Royal Library.
Hey, less creepy mumbling and more searching.
How to become a brother loved by his sister when hundred hexes? Hurry!
Hurry!
Alright, fine, this one.
Marie would probably be sad if I weren't able to heal him.
If Gaush has to know about somebody other than his sister, I'm wondering how to get serious, too.
Charmy and Gray are off looking for new ingredients that might be effective against curses.
Just wait, Asta! We'll bring back delicious goodies that will not only cure your curse, but will fill your tummy, too!
I've never seen that before, but it smells so yummy! Maybe just a little dazed?
No, I have to be strong for Asta!
Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah!
Woo!
Caught creation magic!
Now she bombs it!
We did it!
Let's keep going!
Yeah!
Hard to believe a squad full of misfits and troublemakers would be willing to work so hard, and all for one newbie.
I know. Especially considering that he's an idiotic, reckless, vulgar commoner without any magic.
Stop trying so hard, it's almost getting painful to watch. You're just a grubby little gutter rat who's way out of his depths.
Him, the Wizard King? Talk about delusions of grandeur! You might as well give it all up right now! You are born a loser, you worthless grunt!
He may not have any magic, but he never ever gives up.
He's the first one into battle. Always out there in front, fighting harder than anybody else does.
Jai Vo, Jai Vo, JR
Nickie Lou
Just by being himself, he's done so much.
Asta gave me the strength to fight.
He's helped everybody else, and now it's our turn to help him.
For so long, I've been frustrated because I wasn't blessed with any magic, but instead, I was blessed with friends.
What a bunch of numbskulls. So that's what it takes to actually get those slackers working, huh?
All right, Noelle! It looks like you and I get to work together! Where do you think we should start searching for-
Sorry, I already know where I'm headed, and you're going to take me there. Then you can go search somewhere alone.
Huh? Where do you want to go?
There? Really? All right, your call. I guess they might have some ideas we hadn't thought of.
You know, Vanessa didn't say where she was going. She left before anybody else did.
Well, maybe she had a lead and didn't want to waste any time. Neither do I, for that matter, so let's get going already. What are you waiting for?
Not the best way to ask your superior a favor, but sure.
Coming!
Good, he's home.
We'd like to talk!
Sure. I was just getting out of the bath, so-
Uh…
Oh
How to become a brother loved by his sister 100 hexes
First perform a self-evaluation
Find out what type of big brother you are
Question one
Your sister has a new boyfriend
What do you do?
A. Watch over them from the shadows
B. Actively give her advice
C. Object to him
Period
D. Other
Question two
You see your little sister walking hand in hand with a boy
What do you do?
A. Pretend you're not watching
B. Nod at them, then leave
C. Approach them to strike up a conversation
D. Other
Quiz results
You're a failure as a human being, much less as a big brother?
Reflectory
That's right, Asta! Just keep staying strong! Our magic is never giving up!
Black Clover, page 55
The man named Fonzel
No matter how long it takes or how far we have to go
We will find a way to cure you!
Actively
Not all
A.